RAGE
a rat whispered to me in the subway: "HERETIC"
in the police they stamped "HERETIC" into my passport
"HERETIC" is on my unshaven mug
i love a beautiful knife that leaves no evidence
you're electrocuting my nerves
i don’t trust you today
police baton on my ribs
i'm singing w blood today
in a century we will be resurrected ha
we're those who annoy you today ha
we're getting stronger and it makes u angry
RAGE RAGE RAGE RAGE
I START TO RESIST
how beautiful this world is
i'm a heretic today
my head hurts
i am the third world today
i am a suicide today
i am the third Rome today
i'm a master today
black snow under my feet
fluoxetine annoys me
again I'm under the Major's boot until May
Moscow is Mecca, Siberia is Sinai
RAGE RAGE RAGE RAGE
in "HAMMER OF WITCHES" there is a dedication, it's dedicated to me
i take the power back, i can be dangerous
flying to you on a broomstick ha
you are faithful to the holy inquisition, dear pope
a ricochet will let you down
you tell us that the war is holy
i'm laughing at the stake
i'm going to laugh on the day of my execution because i'll learn about all of or your shady deals
those who judge me today will go missing tomorrow
i'm laughing at the stake
don't you dare to be on my way
666 on my left hand
i'm laughing at the stake
RAGE
They turned off the light
In the entire building the light was turned off
And they said that recording needs to be stopped
Nadya: hi, my name is Tolokonnikova Nadya. What's going on? I'm in charge here.
Police officer: What are you shooting here?
Nadya: We're shooting a music video. What questions you have about the music video?
Police officer: What kind of music video?
Nadya: What video? A good one.
Police officer: Which format?
Nadya: 16:9.
A complaint was received that you are making an UNLAWFUL VIDEO SHOOT
but unlawful video shoot which violates which law?
A video shoot which contains propaganda of homosexuality among minors
LGBT propaganda, inciting hatred...
Police told us that certain things are forbidden
homosexuality is forbidden, thats one
and second...
and what about bisexuality?
they did not say anything about bisexuality
then we're all bisexuals!!
I can go and tell the cops: "Look, leave us alone, we're all bisexuals here, I swear"
and I'll tell them I believe in God!!
We decided to record on our phones
Since we already gathered here
We're going to film our own  "The Blair witch project"!
I hope one day we're going to do what we want freely
Sending love to ya'll
Bro, let me go there!
They put a human in a CAGE
Police officer: We'll be there soon, no worries!
RAGE